Cool, listen to yourself.
You talk like you
just go out there
and buy a luxury car
any time you want.
Ted, a piece of advice.
Maybe try checking
your bank account
before you
start bragging.
Guys, guys, enough.
Today's your
grandpa's birthday.
It's not a circus.
Let's go inside
before this gets ugly.
Yeah, sorry.
Let's go.
Family.
Gotta love them.
Ethan.
Sophia.
Allen.
My boy!
You finally came!
I'm sorry.
I should've come
home a lot sooner.
It's okay.
You're here.
That's all,
you come here.
What is with all
this emotion?
He's been
gone for years
and he's back with
nothing to show for it.
I don't care if he's rich or not, Sophia.
He's healthy,
he's safe.
That's all the matters.
Oh, your health's
nice and all.
But money's what
really matters here.
You know, my son
Allen is already the security manager
of the Knights,
at four hundred
grand a year.
Four hundred grand!
That's more than
the two of you will
ever see in a lifetime.
You know, you
should beg Allen
to give Ted a job.
I mean, unless,
of course,
you just want to be broke like you.
Allen,
could you really
get Ted a job?
Well, um...
Technically,
someone like him
doesn't deserve a spot with the Knights, but
if you beg nicely, I might find him a janitor job.
Janitor job?
That's all you can do is find Ted a janitor job?
You should be grateful
that Allen is even offering him that.
Do you know
how many people
would kill to work
for the Knights now?
Just don't blow it.
Yeah, that's right.
With me in charge,
even cleaning bathrooms
pays better than
whatever he's
doing now.
I don't know.
Tell me, Allen.
How much does this janitor job pay?
Is it over
two million a year?